# Technical Support Engineer / QA-QC Engineer

Full time

Age: 35

City: Lviv



### **Contact Information**

Phone Number: +380977491110

Email: izakharko@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ihor-zakharko-2ab65b49/

#### **About**

10+ years of experience in technical areas: acoustic, low-current, security systems, network and dental equipment.

The path from preparation and installation to training and service.

In search of a vacancy where he could learn new skills and effectively use existing ones.

## **Work Experience**

Technical Support Engineer

from Feb 2018 to now

INSPE, Lviv

**Technical Specialist** 

from Nov 2016 to Feb 2018 (1 year 4 months)

Astra Internet Service Provider. Lviv

#### **Technical Specialist**

from Apr 2013 to Nov 2016 (3 years 8 months)

**Economic Security Agency "EFFORT"**, Lviv

#### Service Engineer

from Oct 2011 to Apr 2013 (1 year 7 months)

UltraHorizont, Lviv

#### **Education**

Lviv Quality Assurance School

Software Tester, QA

2013

Lviv Polytechnic National University

BA, Master, electronic devices, systems and complexes / radio communication, radio and television from 2006 to 2010

Technical College of the National University "Lviv Polytechnic"

Junior specialist, radio engineering

from 2002 to 2006

### **Professional And Other Skills**

- Communication with the support of the manufacturer and customers
- Presentations, exhibitions and events
- Planning and training for service engineers
- Maintaining supporting documentation